

# **ABOUT ME**

I'm a digital designer that can design for web, apps to social media platforms. I think of design as a journey and work with content to optimize experience, whether it's in UX/UI or in visuals. As a designer, I also know when and how to work with prompt engineering and Al tools to enhance designs

In using critical design thinking and research, I'm able to create designs tailored for phones, tablets to large monitors. I have experience with layouts, graphics, product mapping, wireframes, typography and colour









ChatGPT Photoshop Illustrator After Effects





2002









HTML5

2001





2017

ceros ceros

# **EDUCATION**

Mar 2017 - Jun 2017 **General Assembly** (formerly Bitmaker)

Web Development **Program** 

> Web Development Immersive progam

Jan 2001 - Aug 2001 Birmingham City University

# Design course

> UK exchange program selected by Toronto Metropolitan University to partake in Birmingham Aug 2000

**UAL: Central Saint Martins** 

# **Experimentational Design Course**

2000

> Experimentational design course in non-conventional materials and concepts Instructor: Designer Roland Mouret

Sep 1998 - Apr 2002 **Toronto Metropolitan University** (formerly Ryerson University)

# B.A.A. - Fashion Design Degree

> Fashion Design, Fashion Marketing, Consumer Product Design, some Graphic Design

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

with earlier experiences on LinkedIn



#### Senior Designer, Digital & Multimedia • Borden Ladner Gervais LLP • Jan 2020 - Feb 2024

> Creating concepts, visuals and digital products for <u>BLG</u> and subsidiary legal services <u>BLG Beyond</u>; webpages, apps to social media platform visuals; balancing quality, speed, accuracry and consistency in brand standards and goals; Acted as BLG Affinity group committee member (2021 - 2023)



## Digital Designer • Blake, Cassels & Graydon LLP • Aug 2017 - Jan 2020

> Creating digital assets for launch of blakes.com, landing pages, client-facing marketing materials, internal communications, social media channels, print materials



### Design Manager, Consumer Products • Thinkway Toys • Apr 2016 - Mar 2017

> Design Manager in licensed consumer products including Lucas Films Ltd. (Star Wars Rogue One), ©Disney/Pixar (Cars 3), Universal Studios (Despicable Me 3)



# Associate, Online Product Approval • Disney Consumer Products (Disney Canada) • Nov 2013 - Mar 2016

- > Creative associate as part of Disney Canada in the OPA team for consumer softlines and hardllines products sold across Canada; including stores such as Walmart, Target, Canadian Tire, Toy R' Us to Dollarama
- > Working with team in guiding 50+ licensees on 500+ products seasonally including ©Disney/Pixar and Frozen. Managing online product design approvals and meeting with vendors & licensees on communicating design goals and brand guides to defining brand initiatives

# DOLCE & GABBANA

# Associate • Dolce & Gabbana (Milan, Italy) • Feb 2013 - Sept 2013

> Brought 10 years of Canadian design experience abroad and resulted in an opportunity for Dolce & Gabbana in Milan; preparation and assistance on Fall 2013 and Spring 2014 RTW collections, creation of look books